var questions = [
    {
        question: "The School OSUSTECH was established in the year _____?",
        option1: "2004",
        option2: "2010",
        option3: "2009",
        option4: "2011",
        answer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "When did Nigeria gain independence?",
        option1: "1948",
        option2: "1960",
        option3: "1756",
        option4: "1990",
        answer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "The name of the creator of this quiz is",
        option1: "Bankole blackNinja",
        option2: "Adams sajiCode",
        option3: "Kazeem silentWolf",
        option4: "Caleb Sweden",
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of this is not a front end framework",
        option1: "jQuery",
        option2: "Vue",
        option3: "Laravel",
        option4: "Angular",
        answer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "The laptop brand of the author of this quiz is______?",
        option1: "Acer Aspire",
        option2: "MacBook Air",
        option3: "Lenovo Touchpad",
        option4: "Dell Inspirion",
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of this is not a viral disease",
        option1: "SARS-CoV2",
        option2: "COVID-19",
        option3: "Ebola",
        option4: "Lassa Fever",
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "In Statistics and Mathematics, Precision and Accuracy are the same...",
        option1: "True",
        option2: "False",
        option3: "Cannot Say",
        option4: "Non of the above",
        answer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a superhero actor?",
        option1: "Neil Warnock",
        option2: "Tom Holland",
        option3: "Chris Hemsworth",
        option4: "Robert Downey Jr",
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "In what year did chelsea last win the Premier League and FA Cup double?",
        option1: "2010",
        option2: "2011",
        option3: "2012",
        option4: "2017",
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "The highest goal scorer in Chelsea history is _________?",
        option1: "Didier Drogba",
        option2: "Frank Lampard",
        option3: "Jimmy Floyd HasselBaink",
        option4: "Eden Hazard",
        answer: "2"
    }
]